instanceEventData[instanceEventData$pos=="OTHER" & instanceEventData$class=="OCCURRENCE",]$eventID
[1] d117e246  d152e2258 d159e725  d162e2370 d166e467  d172e95   d47e703  
[8] d4e256    d65e34   


<s>"If you <EVENT eid="d117e246" class="OCCURRENCE" word_form="find">find</EVENT> sound, healthy companies in <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">Japan</ENAMEX>, they are not  <EVENT eid="d117e247" class="STATE" word_form="for">for</EVENT> sale," <EVENT eid="d117e43" class="REPORTING" word_form="said">said</EVENT> <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">George Watanabe</ENAMEX>, a management-consultant at <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">Tokyo</ENAMEX>-based <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Asia Advisory Services Inc.</ENAMEX> 

   Statistics on acquisitions by foreigners vary in detail, because unlike <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Sansui</ENAMEX>, which is listed on the <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">Tokyo</ENAMEX> and <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">Osaka</ENAMEX> stock exchanges, most of the Japanese companies acquired by foreigners are privately held.</s> 
[1] "\"If you find sound, healthy companies in Japan, they are not for sale,\" said George Watanabe, a management-consultant at Tokyo-based Asia Advisory Services Inc. Statistics on acquisitions by foreigners vary in detail, because unlike Sansui, which is listed on the Tokyo and Osaka stock exchanges, most of the Japanese companies acquired by foreigners are privately held. ~/Dropbox/cope.dissertation/timebank_1_2/data/extra/wsj_0583.tml"

<s>A spokesman for <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Seagram</ENAMEX>, the Montreal wine and spirits concern controlled by the <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Bronfman</ENAMEX> family, <EVENT eid="d159e45" class="REPORTING" word_form="said">said</EVENT> the company will <EVENT eid="d159e46" class="REPORTING" word_form="post">post</EVENT> additional pretax <EVENT eid="d159e725" class="OCCURRENCE" word_form="profit">profit</EVENT> of about <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY"><EVENT eid="d159e728" class="STATE" word_form="$33">$33</EVENT> million</NUMEX> <TIMEX3 tid="d159t157" type="SET" value="P1Y" temporalFunction="false" functionInDocument="NONE" quant="EVERY" word_form="a year">a year</TIMEX3> because of the additional <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Du Pont</ENAMEX> dividends.</s> 
[1] "A spokesman for Seagram, the Montreal wine and spirits concern controlled by the Bronfman family, said the company will post additional pretax profit of about $33 million a year because of the additional Du Pont dividends. ~/Dropbox/cope.dissertation/timebank_1_2/data/extra/wsj_0918.tml"
<s><ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Mr. Schwarz</ENAMEX> also <EVENT eid="d162e57" class="REPORTING" word_form="said">said</EVENT> costs associated with <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">U.S. Trust</ENAMEX>'s planned move to midtown <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">Manhattan</ENAMEX> from <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">Wall Street</ENAMEX> will <EVENT eid="d162e60" class="ASPECTUAL" word_form="continue">continue</EVENT> to be a <EVENT eid="d162e2370" class="OCCURRENCE" word_form="drag">drag</EVENT> on earnings <SIGNAL sid="d162s110" word_form="through">through</SIGNAL> <TIMEX3 tid="d162t116" type="DATE" value="1990" temporalFunction="false" functionInDocument="NONE" word_form="1990">1990</TIMEX3>.</s> 
[1] "Mr. Schwarz also said costs associated with U.S. Trust's planned move to midtown Manhattan from Wall Street will continue to be a drag on earnings through 1990. ~/Dropbox/cope.dissertation/timebank_1_2/data/extra/wsj_0927.tml"
<s>In <TIMEX3 tid="d166t127" type="DURATION" value="P20M" temporalFunction="true" functionInDocument="NONE" endPoint="d166t118" word_form="the past 20 months">the past 20 months</TIMEX3> alone, <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Paul E. Lego, president and chief operating officer</ENAMEX>, <EVENT eid="d166e24" class="REPORTING" word_form="said">said</EVENT> the divestiture of <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$300 million</NUMEX> of slow-growth, low-profit businesses has been more than <EVENT eid="d166e467" class="OCCURRENCE" word_form="offset">offset</EVENT> by <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$600 million</NUMEX> in profitable acquisitions.</s> 
[1] "In the past 20 months alone, Paul E. Lego, president and chief operating officer, said the divestiture of $300 million of slow-growth, low-profit businesses has been more than offset by $600 million in profitable acquisitions. ~/Dropbox/cope.dissertation/timebank_1_2/data/extra/wsj_0973.tml"
<s>"The key to <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Delta</ENAMEX>'s record earnings <EVENT eid="d172e21" class="ASPECTUAL" word_form="continued">continued</EVENT> to be excellent passenger revenue <EVENT eid="d172e95" class="OCCURRENCE" word_form="growth">growth</EVENT>," <EVENT eid="d172e23" class="REPORTING" word_form="said">said</EVENT> <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Thomas Roeck, chief financial officer</ENAMEX>.</s> 
[1] "\"The key to Delta's record earnings continued to be excellent passenger revenue growth,\" said Thomas Roeck, chief financial officer. ~/Dropbox/cope.dissertation/timebank_1_2/data/extra/wsj_1011.tml"
<s><ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">Israel</ENAMEX> has publicly <EVENT eid="d47e240" class="REPORTING" word_form="declared">declared</EVENT> that it will <EVENT eid="d47e241" class="OCCURRENCE" word_form="respond">respond</EVENT> to an Iraqi <EVENT eid="d47e242" class="OCCURRENCE" word_form="attack">attack</EVENT> on <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">Jordan</ENAMEX> because it wo n't <EVENT eid="d47e243" class="OCCURRENCE" word_form="allow">allow</EVENT> <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">Iraq</ENAMEX>'s dangerous army to <EVENT eid="d47e703" class="OCCURRENCE" word_form="take">take</EVENT> control of <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">Jordan</ENAMEX>'s long border with <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">Israel</ENAMEX>.</s> 
[1] "Israel has publicly declared that it will respond to an Iraqi attack on Jordan because it wo n't allow Iraq's dangerous army to take control of Jordan's long border with Israel. ~/Dropbox/cope.dissertation/timebank_1_2/data/extra/WSJ900813-0157.tml"
<s><EVENT eid="d4e256" class="OCCURRENCE" word_form="that">That</EVENT> was <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Eileen Collins</ENAMEX>, after she <EVENT eid="d4e10" class="OCCURRENCE" word_form="flew">flew</EVENT> as the first ever co-pilot.</s> 
[1] "That was Eileen Collins, after she flew as the first ever co-pilot. ~/Dropbox/cope.dissertation/timebank_1_2/data/extra/ABC19980304.1830.1636.tml"
